NAMITA SHAH

LINKEDIN | GITHUB | namitashah1212@gmail.com | +91-6352007588 Seeking Full-time Job Opportunity- IT graduate – On Site, Remote, Hybrid

Objective: To add the values with the technical skills I pursuit and leverage the company growth in developing the scalable Software Applications

Technical Skills

Languages: HTML5 | CSS3 | JavaScript | TypeScript

Frameworks/Libraries/Interface: .NET | ReactJS | React- Native | Express | Expo | NodeJS | Tailwind CSS

Databases: MongoDB | PostgreSQL

Tools: npm | Git | GitHub | SVN | Bitbucket | Mercurial

Cloud Deployment: AWS | Azure

API Integration: REST | GraphQL

Personal Projects:

1. Note-Making Mobile App:

Technology: React-Native, JavaScript, CSS3,

Purpose: Light Note-Making App, made with simple UI/UX design, Async Storage for the users to create, update and delete the notes, real time for tracking and search engine for quick search of notes

2. Travel Mobile Application:

Technology: React-Native, TypeScript, GraphQL, TypeORM, PostgresSQL, ExpressJS, NodeJS,

Purpose: The purpose of this application is to provide a seamless experience for all the users in terms of Planning,

Managing and Travelling, the Beta Version of this app will soon launch for testing.

Deployment: This is deployed on AWS with the EC2 Instance.

Professional Experience

Amitaujas LLP

Full Stack .Net Web Developer

April 2023 - Nov 2023

- Designed & deploy the websites using .Net as the core technology.
- Learned how to setup project, configure DB connection, apply migrations & Handled Exceptions.

H&M Virtual Service PVT LTD

Technical Customer Care Specialists

June 2022 - Oct 2022

• Troubleshoot the issues, consistently met daily targets, earned a five-star rating on Google with positive feedback, and established a strong rapport with upper management.

Training & Certification

LinkedIn Certification Course

March 2023

• Microsoft Azure Az-900 Fundamental Certification Course

Verzeo Pvt Ltd Training

Python with Data-Science

Jun 2022 - Jul 2022